## Chandan Karmakar's Resume

Email: chandan2102@gmail.com

Phone: 9073354514

## **Summary**

Chandan Karmakar is a Full Stack Developer with over 8 years of experience in software development. He possesses in-depth knowledge of a wide range of programming languages, development tools, and software development life cycle (SDLC) stages.

#### **Skills**

- ASP.NET MVC
- ASP.NET Core
- Angular 8
- SQL Server
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- GIT
- HTML
- CSS
- AJAX
- JSON
- MySQL
- Groovy on Grails

### **Experience**

## Senior Engineer at Wipro Limited (03/2022 - Present)

- Contributing to the development and enhancement of new products for clients
- Strong knowledge of JavaScript with object-oriented programming

#### Senior Software Engineer at Bytes and Bits Information Technology (05/2019 - 02/2022)

- Development of new products for clients and enhancement of existing functionalities
- Involved in the development of multiple web applications for various clients

### Senior Software Engineer at Spring and River Pvt. Ltd. (06/2018 - 05/2019)

- Development and enhancements to the existing web portal of clients
- Maintenance and enhancements to the existing web portal of a retail stores chain

# Member of Technical Staff (Software Engineer) at Interra Information Technologies (India) Pvt. Ltd. (07/2014 - 07/2017)

- Responsible for entire scripting workload for browser compatibility project
- · Development, enhancements, and maintenance of loyalty kiosk

#### **Education**

Not provided in the given resume